William Edgar Borah Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Office File, 1907-1940 (Box 1-528)
  - 1916-1917 (Box 37)
    - Sheep experiments station
    - Smith, Stephen M.
    - Social
    - Soldiers homes
    - Tariff
    - Trading with the enemy
    - Treaties
    - University of Idaho, Moscow, Idaho, (2 folders)
    - War inventions
    - War matters
      - General, (3 folders) (Box 46)
    - War matters, peace terms
    - War risk insurance
    - War service applications
      - A-G, (3 folders)
      - H-Z, (6 folders) (Box 47)
    - War situation speech, (4 folders) (Box 48)
    - War tax, (2 folders)
    - Webb-Pomerene Trade Bill
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military academy
    - Woman suffrage
    - Wool, fixing the price of
    - Wyman, Frank
  - 1917-1918 (Box 49)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Agricultural matters
    - Applications for pardons
    - Applications for positions, (3 folders)
    - Army matters
      - Complaints
      - Discharges, (3 folders)
      - General, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 50)
      - Inquiries, (4 folders)
      - Medical
    - Austin, Mark
    - Barber, O. H.
    - Borah, Charles F.
    - Burrell, E. A.
    - Business, (3 folders)
    - Capital Issues Committee
    - Cavanah, Charles C. (Box 51)
    - Censorship
    - Charity
    - Childrens Loyalty League
    - Citizenship
    - Claims
    - Conduct of the war
    - Congratulations, (2 folders)
    - Congressional Record
    - Conscription
    - Cotton situation
    - Court-martial bill
    - Crozier, Alfred O.
    - Davis, D. W. (Box 52)
    - Dewey, Edward H.
    - District of Columbia matters
    - Documents
      - Agricultural yearbook, (3 folders)
      - Labor
      - Maps
      - Miscellaneous, (3 folders)
      - School (Box 53)
    - Draft inquiries, (2 folders)
    - Dubois, Fred T.
    - Educational matters
    - Espionage, (2 folders)
    - Evans, Evan
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal courts
    - Federal Farm Loan Board
    - Federal judges
    - Fish
    - Food Administration
      - Farm labor
      - General
      - Grain bags
      - Potatoes (Box 54)
      - Wheat, (3 folders)
    - Fuel Administration
    - General information
    - Gipson, James H.
    - Hart, John W.
    - Hawley, James H.
    - Hay
    - Hays, Will
    - Heigho, Edgar M.
    - Immigration
    - Indian affairs
    - Insurance, war risk (Box 55)
    - Internal Revenue
    - Invitations, Alabama-Wisconsin, (27 folders)
    - Invitations to join organizations
    - Japanese-Siberian problem
    - Jenkins, Francis
    - Labor matters
    - Lasley, A. M. (Box 56)
    - Legislation, miscellaneous
    - Letters of introduction
    - Liberty Bonds
    - Lists
    - Loyalty
    - McConnell, William J.
    - Mail clerk salaries
    - Martin, Frank
    - Mexican matters
    - Miscellaneous
      - General, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 57)
      - War, (2 folders)
    - National banks
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md., (2 folders)
    - Navy matters, discharge, (2 folders) (Box 58)
      - Discharges
      - General
    - Newspapers
    - Non-Partisan League
    - Osteopathic bill, (3 folders)
    - Overman bill
    - Oversmith, A. H.
    - Pardons (Box 59)
    - Parkhurst, W. S.
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Peace terms
    - Pension legislation, (2 folders)
    - Politics
      - A-J, (3 folders)
      - K-Z, (3 folders) (Box 60)
    - Post Office Department
    - Postal laws, zone system
    - Postal legislation, zone system
    - Price fixing, metals and wood
    - Profiteering, (2 folders)
    - Prohibition, (3 folders) (Box 61)
    - Protests against appointments
    - Public ownership of utilities
    - Purcell, L. I.
    - Railway matters
    - Red Cross
    - Religious matters
    - Requests for photographs
    - Revenue law
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Roads (Box 62)
    - Robertson, John D.
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Rural credits
    - Russian situation
    - Sheridan, R. Story
    - Sinclair, Bartlett
    - Social
    - Spangenberg, P. H.
    - Speech on war issue, 18 Mar. 1918, (2 folders)
    - State appointments
    - Taylor, S. D. (Box 63)
    - Timber interests
    - Transportation, (2 folders)
    - Treaties, (2 folders)
    - Trusts
    - U.S. marshall
    - Universal military training
    - University of Idaho, Moscow, Idaho
    - War inventions
    - War service applications
      - A-B, (2 folders)
      - B-G, (5 folders) (Box 64)
      - H-P, (5 folders) (Box 65)
      - Q-Z, (5 folders) (Box 66)
    - War tax
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military academy, (2 folders)
    - Whitla, Ezra R.
    - Woman suffrage, (7 folders) (Box 67)
    - Wyman, Frank T.
  - 1918-1919 (Box 68)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Alaska matters
    - American Honor Roll Co.
    - Anonymous
    - Applications for positions, (2 folders)
    - Appreciation letters
    - Army matters
      - General
      - Inquiries, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 69)
    - Austin, Mark
    - Borah, Charles F.
    - Boy Scouts
    - Bureau of War Risk
    - Business
    - Cannons, applications for
    - Capital Issues Committee
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charity
    - Citizenship
    - Claims (Box 70)
    - Cobb, Calvin
    - Cold storage
    - Committee meetings
    - Congressional Record
    - Court-martial cases, (5 folders)
    - Cranks
    - Daylight savings time
    - Demobilization (Box 71)
    - Dewey, Edward H.
    - Discharges
      - Army
        - A-K, (4 folders)
        - L-W, (4 folders) (Box 72)
      - Navy (Box 73)
        - A-R, (6 folders)
        - T-W, (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Documents
      - General, (3 folders)
      - Legislative
      - Schools
      - Yearbook
    - Draft boards
    - Eagleson, John W.
    - Education legislation
    - Educational matters
    - Espionage
    - Evans, Evan
    - Explosives, regulation of (Box 75)
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal courts
    - Federal Farm Loan Board
    - Federal judges
    - Federal Reserve banks
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Fish
    - Flenner, Guy
    - Food Administration
    - Foreign affairs
    - General services and information
    - Hart, John W.
    - High cost of living
    - Immigration
    - Indian affairs
    - Internal Revenue Service, (2 folders)
    - International finance
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations
      - California-League of Nations, (8 folders)
      - Maryland-Wisconsin, (12 folders) (Box 76)
    - Invitations to join organizations
    - Labor matters, (2 folders)
    - League to Enforce Peace
    - Leak inquiry
    - Legislation
    - Letters of recommendation
    - Liberty Bonds
    - Lists
    - McConnell, William J.
    - Mail frauds
    - Meat trust
    - Metric system
    - Mexican affairs (Box 77)
    - Miscellaneous
      - General, (3 folders)
      - War
    - National banks
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Naval affairs
      - General
      - Inquiries
    - Newspapers, magazines (Box 78)
    - Panama Canal
    - Pardons
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Peace terms
    - Pension legislation
    - Politics
    - Postal laws
    - Price fixing
      - Miscellaneous
      - Hogs, wheat, and wool
    - Primary law
    - Profiteering
    - Prohibition
    - Protests against appointments
    - Public ownership of utilities (Box 79)
    - Railroads, (2 folders)
    - Removal of bodies
    - Requests for photographs
    - Requests for speeches
    - Revenue bill
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Roads, (3 folders)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore, memorial
    - Russian matters
    - Sailors and soldiers bonus
    - Social
    - State appointments (Box 80)
    - Tariff
    - Time zones
    - Transportation matters
    - Treaties
    - Trusts
    - University of Idaho, Moscow, Idaho
    - Vivisection
    - Vocational education
    - War inventions
    - War miscellaneous
    - War risk insurance
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military academy
    - Woman suffrage, (2 folders)
    - Wyman, Frank
  - 1919-1920 (Box 81)
    - Agriculture Department
    - Applications for positions, (2 folders)
    - Army matters, (2 folders)
    - Boise barracks, Boise, Idaho
    - Business, (2 folders)
    - Cannons
    - Citizenship
    - Claims, (4 folders) (Box 82)
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Record
    - Conscientious objectors
    - Convention matters
    - Court-martial cases
    - Davis, Edwin G.
    - Discharge certificates
    - Discharges
      - Army
      - Navy
    - Documents
    - Educational matters
    - Espionage
    - Explosives
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal courts
    - Fish
    - Food control
    - Foreign affairs (Box 83)
    - General information
    - Immigration
    - Income tax
    - Indian affairs
    - Internal Revenue
    - International finance
    - Interstate Commerce Commission
    - Invitations, (22 folders)
    - Japanese question
    - Labor matters
    - League of Nations
    - Legislation
    - Letters of introduction
    - Liberty Bonds (Box 84)
    - Merchant marine
    - Mexican matters
    - Military training
    - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Navy matters
    - Newspapers
    - Panama Canal
    - Pardons
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal (Box 85)
    - Politics (by state)
      - Alabama-Idaho, S, (14 folders)
      - Illinois-Virginia, (28 folders) (Box 86)
      - Washington-Wisconsin, (4 folders) (Box 87)
    - Post Office Department
    - Profiteering
    - Prohibition
    - Protests against appointments
    - Public health
    - Railroad Administration
    - Railway matters
    - Requests for photographs
    - Requests for speeches
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Roads
    - Rural credits
    - Russian matter
    - Seed distribution
    - Shipping Board
    - Social
    - Soldiers bonus
    - Tariff
    - Treaties
    - Trusts
    - Versailles Treaty
    - Vocational education
    - War risk insurance
    - West Point, N.Y., United States Military academy
    - Woman suffrage
    - Wool
  - 1920-1921 (Box 88)
    - Aeronautics
    - Agricultural Capital Bill
    - Agriculture pepa
    - Aircraft
    - American Legion, repeal of character
    - Applications for pardons
    - Applications for positions, (7 folders)
    - Appropriations (Box 89)
      - military
      - miscellaneous
    - Armenian question
    - Army matters, (3 folders)
    - Army, reduction of
    - Austin, Mark
    - Babb, James E.
    - Banks
    - Blue laws
    - Boise barracks, Boise, Idaho
    - Bonus, federal employees
    - Budget system
    - Bursam Bill
    - Business, (1 folder) (Box 90)
    - Capper Bill (S. 4613)
    - Caribbean and Dominican situation
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charity
    - Citizenship
    - Civil rights bill
    - Civil Service reclassification
    - Claims, (2 folders)
    - Clothing workers
    - Coal
    - Cohalan, Daniel F.
    - Columbian Treaty
    - Committee assignments
    - Condolence letters
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library list
    - Congressional Record
    - Conscientious objectors
    - Costa Rica resolution (Box 91)
    - Court-martial cases, (2 folders)
    - Cusick, J. J.
    - Deportations
    - Disarmament
      - Alabama
      - Arkansas
      - California
      - Colorado
      - Conference, (2 folders)
      - Connecticut
      - District of Columbia
      - Florida
      - Fullam, W. F.
      - Idaho, (2 folders)
      - Illinois
      - Indiana
      - Iowa (Box 92)
      - Kansas
      - Maine
      - Maryland
      - Massachusetts
      - Michigan
      - Minnesota
      - Miscellaneous
      - Missouri
      - Nebraska
      - Newfoundland
      - New Hampshire
      - New Jersey
      - New York (state)
      - New York (city), (2 folders)
      - North Carolina
      - North Dakota
      - Ohio
      - Oklahoma
      - Oregon
      - Pennsylvania
      - South Dakota
      - Tennessee
      - Texas
      - Utah
      - Vermont
      - Virginia
      - Washington
      - Wisconsin
    - Discharge
      - Army
      - Marine
      - Navy
    - Discharge certificates
    - Documents
    - Educational matters
    - Espionage
    - Explosives (Box 93)
    - Export trade
    - Farm Loan Act
    - Federal buildings
    - Federal courts
    - Federal farm loan
    - Federal Reserve Act, (2 folders)
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Federal Trade Commission, (2 folders)
    - Fess Bill
    - Finance
    - Fish
    - Food control
    - Foreign affairs
    - Freight rates, (2 folders)
    - Funding of foreign debt (Box 94)
    - General information, (2 folders)
    - German treaty
    - Gold and silver
    - Good roads
    - Grain trading bill
    - Gwinn, Monte
    - Hamer, Thomas R.
    - Harris, bill
    - Hart, John W.
    - Hawaiian legislation
    - Immigration
    - Inaugural expenses
    - Inauguration
    - Income tax
    - Indian affairs (Box 95)
    - Internal Revenue
    - International finance
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, (2 folders)
    - Invitations (by state)
      - Alabama-New Jersey, (22 folders)
      - New York-Wisconsin, (12 folders) (Box 96)
    - Irish question, (2 folders)
    - Japanese question
    - Justice Department
    - Knox Resolution
    - Ku Klux Klan
    - Labor
    - Land offices
    - Lesley, Sue
    - Legislation, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 97)
    - Legislative record
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Liberty Bonds
    - Linney, Frank A., (3 folders)
    - Lists
    - Livestock industry
    - Long and short haul
    - Longshoreman's compensation bill
    - McConnell, William J.
    - Merchant marine
    - Mexican matters
    - Miscellaneous, (7 folders) (Box 98)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National banks
    - Naturalization
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Navy
      - General
      - Legislation (Box 99)
    - Newberry case
    - Newspapers, (4 folders)
    - O'Hare, Kate Richards
    - Panama Canal
    - Passports
    - Patents
    - Patronage, Alfred Budge, appointment as judge
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal
    - Philippine
      - Legislation
      - Situation
    - Pocatello Internal Revenue Office, Pocetello, Idaho (Box 100)
    - Politics, (2 folders)
    - Post Office Department
      - Employees
      - General
      - Legislation
    - Price-fixing movement
    - Primary law
    - Profiteering
    - Prohibition, (2 folders)
    - Public health
    - Public Health Service
    - Public Welfare Department
    - Railroads, (2 folders)
    - Recommendations and letters of introduction (Box 101)
    - Rent bill, District of Columbia
    - Requests for speeches
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Robertson, John D.
    - Rockwell, Irvin E.
    - Russia
    - Salaries, increase of
    - Samoa, conditions
    - Seeds
    - Sheppard-Towner bill
    - Sheridan, R. Story
    - Shipping Board
    - Sims' matter
    - Smith-Towner bill
    - Social
    - Soldiers legislation, (2 folders) (Box 102)
    - Sterling sedition bill
    - Strikes
    - Tariff
      - Agriculture and livestock interests
      - Almonds
      - Aluminum
      - Amorphous graphite
      - Bags and burlap
      - Barytes ore
      - Beets
      - Books
      - Brick
      - Butter and eggs
      - Coal tar products
      - Cocoa mats and mattings
      - Cotton
      - Dressed beef and hides
      - Dried peas
      - Dye industry
      - Fine tool steels
      - Flax straw
      - Frozen beef
      - Furniture
      - General
      - Gold leaf
      - Honey
      - Lead
      - Lemons
      - Lumber
      - Magnesite (Box 103)
      - Mica
      - Motion pictures
      - Oil
      - Olives
      - Peas and beans
      - Poles
      - Potato flour
      - Poultry
      - Pumice
      - Sausage
      - Seeds
      - Sugar, Cuban
      - Tobacco
      - Tungsten
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Tariff and embargo
      - Farm, (2 folders)
      - Wheat
      - Wool
      - Miscellaneous
    - Taxes
      - Alcohol
      - Candy
      - Carpets
      - Cork insulation
      - Excess profits
      - Excise
      - Exempt securities
      - Federal and state
      - Federal license on cars
      - Hotels
      - Import
      - Income
      - Insurance premiums
      - Jewelry
      - Legislation
      - Luxury (Box 104)
      - Medicines
      - "Milk-filled" products
      - Musical instruments
      - Non-alcoholic liquors
      - Passports
      - Personal
      - Pyrites
      - Reimportation of goods formerly sent to France
      - Sales
      - Silver foxes
      - Syrup
      - Wallpaper
    - Towner-Sterling Bill See Container 101, Smith-Towner Bill
    - Transfers
    - Treaties
    - Trusts
    - Unemployment
    - Vocational education
    - Voluntary parenthood
    - War Finance Corp.
    - West Point, N. Y., United States Military Academy
    - Woman suffrage
    - Wyman, Frank
    - Yellowstone Dam, Mont.
    - Zone system
  - 1921-1922 (Box 105)
    - Aeronautics (S.J. Res. 77)
    - Agriculture
      - Borah Bill (S. 1042)
      - Conference
      - Interests, price fixing
      - Legislation
      - Agriculture Department
    - Air Service, Gen. Martin
    - Alien property custodian, (2 folders)
    - American Expeditionary Force
    - Amnesty, Federal political prisoners, (2 folders)
    - Antigambling bills
    - Antilynching bill (Dyer Bill), (3 folders) (Box 106)
    - Applications
      - Pardons, (2 folders)
      - Positions
        - A-L, (2 folders)
        - M-Z (Box 107)
    - Appointments
    - Appropriations
      - General
      - Military
    - Armenian situation
    - Army, (2 folders)
    - Articles, requests for, (2 folders)
    - Articles, requests for, granted
    - Assay office, Boise, Idaho (Box 108)
    - Babb, James E.
    - Balfour note concerning Bernard Baruch letters
    - Ball Rent Control Act
    - Bank legislation
    - Bannerman, Francis, gift
    - Blanket amendment
    - Blue sky law
    - Boise barracks, Boise, Idaho
    - Bonus, federal employees
    - Borah, Charles F.
    - Bursum bill
      - Disabled soldiers
      - Indian land bill
    - Business
      - Income tax
      - Insurance policies
      - Lodge dues
      - Taxes
      - Miscellaneous
    - Cabinet
    - Capper Bill (S. 2531)
    - Car (railroad) shortage
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charity
    - Charters, requests for
    - Child Labor Law
    - Citizenship
    - Civil Rights bills (S. 664, S. 1375)
    - Civil Service, reclassification of
    - Claims, (2 folders) (Box 109)
    - Clothing workers, investigation of
    - Coal bill, (3 folders)
    - Coal Commission
    - Committee
      - Assignments
      - Educational matters
      - Eight-hour day
      - General
      - Resolutions, Semonov, (4 folders) (Box 110)
      - Miscellaneous
    - Condolences
    - Congratulatory letters
    - Congressional Record
    - Court-martial cases
    - Cravath, P. D.
    - Daugherty, Harry M., impeachment of
    - Dewey, Edward H.
    - Disarmament conference, (2 folders)
    - Discharges (Box 111)
      - Army
      - Certificates
      - Marine Corps
      - Navy
    - District suffrage
    - Documents
    - Education
    - Espionage
    - Explosives
    - Export trade
    - Farm Loan Act
    - Federal buildings, courts, and judges
    - Federal farm loan
    - Federal Reserve Act
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - Federal Trade Commission
    - Financial conditions (Box 112)
    - Fish
    - Foreign affairs
      - Clemenceau (Nov. 1922)
      - Debt, funding of
      - Europe
      - Miscellaneous
    - Four Power Treaty, (3 folders)
    - Freight rates (Box 113)
    - Game legislation
    - General information, (3 folders)
    - Genoa Conference
    - Gold and silver
    - Good roads
    - Government Grain Corp., revival of, (2 folders)
    - Governments, different forms of
    - Haiti and Caribbean situation, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 114)
    - Hart, John W.
    - Hileman, Grace
    - Horn, Brook E. J.
    - Immigration
    - Increase in salary
    - Indian
      - Affairs
      - Legislation
    - Integrity of the states
    - Internal Revenue
    - Interstate Commerce
    - Intolerance
    - Invitations (by Ssate)
      - Alabama-Georgia, (9 folders)
      - Idaho-New York, (19 folders) (Box 115)
      - North Carolina-Wisconsin, (12 folders) (Box 116)
    - Irish question
    - Jacobsen, N. A
    - Justice Department
    - Labor matters
    - Ladd Bill (S. 2342)
    - Lansing, Robert H., Ishii Agreement
    - Lawlessness
    - Lawson, Harry A.
    - Legislation, (1 folder) (Box 117)
    - Legislative record
    - Letters of introduction
    - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Liberal party
    - Liberty Bonds
    - Librarian loan, J. P. Morgan letter
    - Lists
    - McDonald, James G.
    - Mail contracts
    - Marsters, Elias
    - Merchant marine and ship subsidy
    - Mexico
    - Military training
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 118)
    - Muscle Shoals, Ala.
    - National Bank
    - Naval academy, Annapolis, Md.
    - Naval affairs
    - Newberry case
    - Newspapers and magazines, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 119)
    - Nicaragua
    - Nine Power Treaty
    - Outlawing of war
    - Palestine situation
    - Panama Canal
    - Passports
    - Patent Office
    - Patents
    - Pension legislation
    - Personal
    - Philippine legislation
    - Photographs
    - Political (Box 120)
      - Idaho, (2 folders)
      - Personal
      - Third party movement
      - Miscellaneous
    - Post Office
    - Potter, William
    - Primary law, (2 folders)
    - Prohibition
    - Public health (Box 121)
    - Railroads, (2 folders)
    - Recommendation, letters of
    - Requests for speeches
    - Rhineland troops, Germany
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Russia
    - Schreiner, George A.
    - Seeds
    - Seized property, German
    - Ship subsidy (Box 122)
    - Soldier bonus (inquiries by state)
      - Alabama-New Jersey, (24 folders)
      - New York-Wisconsin, (17 folders) (Box 123)
    - Soldier legislation, (4 folders)
    - Soldiers Home, Washington, D.C.
    - Strikes (Box 124)
    - Sundsmo, Albert, affair
    - Tariff, (5 folders)
    - Tax associations (Box 125)
    - Taxes, (2 folders)
    - Teapot Dome Scandal
    - Towne-Sterling Educational Bill, (2 folders)
    - Transfers
    - Unemployment
    - United States Shipping Board
    - Versailles Treaty
    - Veterans Bureau
    - Veterans hospitals
    - Vocational education, (1 folder) (Box 126)
    - Voigt Milk Bill
    - War Finance Corp.
    - War risk insurance
    - West Point, N. Y., United States Military Academy
    - White, William Allen
  - 1922-1923 (Box 127)
    - Agricultural conditions
    - Agriculture Department
    - Agriculture finance
    - Alaskan fisheries
    - Alien property custodian
    - Amnesty
    - Anti-Lynching bill
    - Applications
      - Pardons, (2 folders)
      - Positions
        - A-I, (4 folders)
        - J-Z, (3 folders) (Box 128)
    - Appointments, (2 folders)
    - Appropriations
    - Army, (2 folders)
    - Articles, (3 folders)
    - Babb, James E. (Box 129)
    - Birth control
    - Blue sky law
    - Boise barracks, Boise, Idaho
    - Bursum Bill, (3 folders)
    - Business
      - Lodge dues
      - Taxes
      - Miscellaneous
    - Capital News, sale of
    - Cavanah, Charles C.
    - Charities
    - Chester concessions in Turkey
    - Child labor law
    - Citizenship
    - Claims, (3 folders) (Box 130)
    - Coal Commission
    - Committee
      - Frelinghuysen Bill
      - Miscellaneous
    - Condolence letters
    - Congratulations
    - Congressional Library list
    - Congressional Record
    - Constitution
    - Court martial cases
    - Dewey, Edward H.
    - Disarmament
    - Discharges (Box 131)
      - Army
      - Certificates
      - Marine Corps
      - Navy
    - Documents
      - General
      - Levinson, Salmon O.
    - Dubois, Fred T.
    - Education
    - Explosives